<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>product on The bugalore</title>
    <link>https://niharika29.github.io/tags/product/</link>
    <description>Recent content in product on The bugalore</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://niharika29.github.io/tags/product/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project] TemplateWizard for WikiEditor</title>
      <link>https://niharika29.github.io/post/template-wizard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niharika29.github.io/post/template-wizard/</guid>
      <description>One of the perks of working at an open source organization like mine is that I get to talk about my work projects with the world. Everything I do as part of my work is public and accessible to anyone who wishes to see it.
TemplateWizard is one of the first projects I undertook as a Product Manager that has major user-facing functionality. The project was requested during the 2017 Community Wishlist Survey and made it to #5 in the results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project] Introducing global preferences across Wikimedia projects</title>
      <link>https://niharika29.github.io/post/global-preferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niharika29.github.io/post/global-preferences/</guid>
      <description>Note: This post was originally published on https://wikimediafoundation.org/2018/09/06/global-preferences-wikimedia-wikis/
There are a lot of Wikimedia wikis. Wikipedia is the best-known of them all, but there&amp;rsquo;s also Commons, Wikiquote, Wikisource, Wiktionary, and more.
Also, each of these sites is available in multiple languages. Wikipedia, for example, has nearly 300 language editions. The newest launched just this week.
Until this month, each wiki and language version had individual preference settings. This caused some serious frustration for people who contribute to multiple wikis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a Product Manager</title>
      <link>https://niharika29.github.io/post/becoming-a-pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niharika29.github.io/post/becoming-a-pm/</guid>
      <description>After three years and five months of being a software engineer at Wikimedia, I decided to step into the role of a product manager at Wikimedia in April 2018. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t an abrupt change. I&amp;rsquo;d been toying with managing products since early 2017 and I was lucky to have a manager who was willing to give me a chance. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of good advice out there about how to transition into product manager which you will undoubtedly find helpful if you&amp;rsquo;re looking to make the switch.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>