<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The bugalore</title>
    <link>https://niharika29.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The bugalore</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Powered by frustration, passion and [Hugo](http://gohugo.io).</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://niharika29.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a Product Manager</title>
      <link>https://niharika29.github.io/post/becoming-a-pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niharika29.github.io/post/becoming-a-pm/</guid>
      <description>After three years and five months of being a software engineer at Wikimedia, I decided to step into the role of a product manager at Wikimedia in April 2018. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t an abrupt change. I&amp;rsquo;d been toying with managing products since early 2017 and I was lucky to have a manager who was willing to give me a chance. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of good advice out there about how to transition into product manager which you will undoubtedly find helpful if you&amp;rsquo;re looking to make the switch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resurrecting a MediaWiki instance</title>
      <link>https://niharika29.github.io/post/mediawiki-backup-restore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niharika29.github.io/post/mediawiki-backup-restore/</guid>
      <description>This was my first time backing up and setting up a new MediaWiki (-vagrant) instance from scratch so I decided to document it in the hope that future me might find it useful.
We (teams at Wikimedia) often use MediaWiki-Vagrant instances on Labs, err, Cloud VPS to test and demonstrate our projects. It&amp;rsquo;s also pretty handy to be able to use it when one&amp;rsquo;s local dev environment is out of order (way more common than you&amp;rsquo;d think).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s a senior developer?</title>
      <link>https://niharika29.github.io/post/good-developer-bad-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niharika29.github.io/post/good-developer-bad-developer/</guid>
      <description>Something at work today prompted me to get thinking about what people generally mean when they say they are/someone is a senior developer.
There are some things which are a given - long-term technical experience, fairly good knowledge of complex languages and codebases, past experience working on products and so on.
But in my opinion, there are a fair number of things which we don&amp;rsquo;t really talk about but are important skills a &amp;ldquo;senior&amp;rdquo; developer must possess to actually deserve that title.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Eventlogging adventure</title>
      <link>https://niharika29.github.io/post/eventlogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niharika29.github.io/post/eventlogging/</guid>
      <description>What the heck is eventlogging? Eventlogging is a MediaWiki extension which lets us log events such as how users interact with a certain feature (client-side logging) or capturing the state of a system (user, permissions etc.) when a certain event happens (server-side logging). There are 3 different parts to eventlogging an event. The schema, the code and the log data. I won&amp;rsquo;t be going into the details of that because there&amp;rsquo;s a detailed guide for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog? Bleurgh.</title>
      <link>https://niharika29.github.io/post/blog-bleurgh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niharika29.github.io/post/blog-bleurgh/</guid>
      <description>The what, the why, the when, the who, the how: I&amp;rsquo;ve been coding for a while now, mostly on Wikimedia projects. Every time I get stuck with a bug or come across something I didn&amp;rsquo;t know of, I&amp;rsquo;d learn something new, fix it and move on. While this works great for me, it&amp;rsquo;s a wealth of knowledge that I&amp;rsquo;m keeping all to myself. I wanted to be able to pass on the intriguing lessons I learnt to other people who might want to hear the stories I brought back from the pits I fell into (no, not like Bruce Wayne).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>